gamebox.com 2017-06-24

# GameBox | Play Free Games | Privacy Policy

Your privacy is the highest priority to us. To help protect your privacy we provide this overview explaining our online practices and the options you can choose regarding the data and information collected. This form applies to all information collected from or submitted to www.gamebox.com   
Application of This Notice 

This Notice applies only to the information collected from the users of www.gamebox.com. It does not apply to information collected in any other way, including any FTP (Free to Play) services.   
The Information We Collect 

Personal information you provide to us when using WWW.GAMEBOX.COM, such as your e-mail address will be kept strictly confidential and only used to customize personal settings, and to notify you of special offers, updated information and new products and services. Circumstances may arise where we are required to disclose your personal information by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. We will send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt out of receiving further marketing from WWW.GAMEBOX.COM by emailing us at: gameboxcsteam@gmail.com 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data precision, and ensure the correct use of information, we have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

 With regard to VIPs, your information will be kept confidential and will solely be used for verification and will not be used for any other purpose. Your details will not be sold or passed on to third parties. Always check and confirm any messages you receive sent by our GM regarding Super Membership. 

 With regard to Facebook users, your information when registering through Facebook will be kept highly confidential. We will only use your name, user ID and gender. 

 At any time you can request personal information to be removed from our databases or you can manually remove information yourself. You can also unsubscribe your registration. 

If you would like to contact us for more information regarding our privacy practices, please e-mail us at the following address: gameboxcsteam@gmail.com
